Посещаемость
Так, завтра начинаются летние каникулы!
Не беситесь сильно. Всем ясно?
Слышь,
погнали завтра на пляж.
А, давай.
Мне, внезапно, захотелось арбуза!
К чему бы это?
Давайте плеваться семечками.
Давай-давай!
Велосипед
на Двоих
«Велосипед на двоих»
Уже завтра каникулы.
`
О, да, Вот они, долгожданные каникулы!
Никакой школы, можно играть сколько влезет!
Займись лучше домашкой.
«Завтра только первый день каникул,
так что можно забить», — так думал?
Как догадалась?!
Значит, я права?
Н-Но ведь каникулы созданы для веселья.
Бассейн или, там, пляж. А ещё походы и всё такое.
Времени совсем в обрез!
Вот бы летние каникулы никогда не кончались!
Даже так?
А мне нравится школа.
Ведь…
там весело.
Летние каникулы, да?
Жарень!
Такой приятный ветерок.
Прибавь ещё скорости!
Не проси невозможного, я и так спёкся.
Жара…
Может и нам попробовать?
Э?!
Естественно, ты за рулём.
Нет, ни за что!
Так ведь, машина может сбить. Опасно!
Здесь нет машин и это не общественная дорога.
Но ведь…
Что такое? Неужели застеснялся?
К-Конечно же нет!
А, значит просто не умеешь.
О чём это ты? Вдвоём на велике проще простого же.
Но, всё таки, это опасно. Лучше не стоит.
Тогда пошли на пустырь.
Э?
Если не сможешь, с тебя сок.
Смотри же, Такаги-сан.
Совместная езда - легкотня!
Стой, это не считается!
Я смогу!
С тебя сок.
Погодь! Погодь!
Н-Неужели совместная езда такая трудная?!
Такаги-сан, ты ведь держишь равновесие?
Держу, конечно.
Уверена?
Сижу как обычно.
Не едем мы только из-за тебя, Нисиката.
Ведь, последний раз, когда меня так катали,
мой партнёр плавно крутил педали.
Э-Э? Вот это да.
Подруга?
Не-а. Это была не девочка.
А…
Ещё раз. У меня почти получилось.
Ах ты!
Сейчас-то получится!
Чёрт… И почему я так расстроился!
Да что это такое?
Ты как-то стал агрессивнее?
Нифига не агрессинее!
Я просто не хочу покупать тебе сок!
Именно, я просто не хочу покупать ей сок.
Только и всего!
Ого, поехали.
Знаешь, Нисиката,
последний раз вот так меня катал
мой папа.
Э?
Мне, вроде как, было 4 годика.
Держи.
Спасибо.
Вкуснятина!
Нисиката, а ты не будешь?
А, ну…
Да, я… это… обойдусь.
Нельзя говорить, что денег не хватает.
Виноградный Сидр
Будешь?
Нет… всё в порядке.
Опять начнёт затирать про непрямой поцелуй,
чтоб поиздеваться!
Не обманывай себя. Попробуй.
Я, правда, не хочу.
Терпение.
Нужно выстоять.
Держи, иначе схватишь тепловой удар.
Э? М-Можно?
Угу,
так ведь…
Нисиката, ты так стесняешься непрямого поцелуя.
Д-Да не в этом дело!
Правда чтоли?
Я-Я тебе говорю!
Ж-Жарко-то как.
Спасибо за напиток.
We won't be walking home
from school for a while.
Well, yeah. It's summer vacation.
Придумала.
Starting from tomorrow, let's practice
tandem riding here until noon.
Huh?
I guess it's okay. But not on the road.
Yeah, we'll just ride here.
If we're only riding here, there's
no point in practicing, don't you think?
No, there is.
Summer vacation starts tomorrow.
What do you mean?
Well, then! Let's go home.
Summer vacation, huh?
I can't wait for summer vacation.
You're saying that now?
Первый
День
Летних
Каникул
«Первый день летних каникул»
To think it would rain on the first
day of summer vacation…
`
My summer vacation plans are ruined!
It's just for a day. Who cares?
`
I was supposed to go to the pool today.
I'm never getting the time back!
`
Stop crying.
There's nothing we can do about the rain.
Let's start our homework.
Huh?
What do you mean, "Huh?"
Don't tell me you didn't bring your homework.
I told you we should do our homework since
we can't do anything because of the rain!
I thought I misheard you.
Why?!
Why do we have homework during
summer vacation in the first place?!
Don't you think that's wrong?!
We can't have a vacation during vacation.
Right?
But we do have homework,
so we have to do it.
Oh, jeez! Юкари-тян,
quit doing your homework and relax!
Doing your homework in front of me
reminds me of homework,
and I can't enjoy myself!
Not my problem!
You should be reminded of homework!
It's only the first day.
Just forget about homework.
That's typical of a person who will be
crying with regret on August 31st.
You're so stubborn!
I'm just gonna read manga, so there.
100% Unrequited Love
Whatever…
Юкари-тян…
Can we write our book report on manga?
That's it!
Can you two just go home?
Test of Courage
"Test of Courage."
Good, it stopped raining.
Wait, why am I happy about that?
Нисиката.
You're here.
Yeah, we made a promise.
I guess so.
Is something wrong?
Uh, n-no… It's nothing.
Wow, so many puddles.
It really poured last night, huh?
I didn't recognize her for a second there.
Come to think of it, I ran into her
coincidentally a few times on our days off,
but this is our first time meeting up.
Could this be what people call a date?!
No, no! That's not what this is!
We're just practicing tandem riding.
Нисиката.
Wh-What is it?
Were you listening?
S-Sorry, what did you say?
We can't tandem ride in this condition.
Uh, yeah…
I was planning to go out in the
afternoon right after our practice.
It's a pain to go back home, so will
you hang out with me to kill some time?
I-Is this… a date?!
No, no, no, no…
I guess so. But someplace
where there aren't many people.
There's no telling what our classmates
would say if any of them saw us.
Hmm…
Then… How about…
A test of courage?
Perfect for summer, right?
Isn't it usually done at night?
Don't worry. I heard it's really dark in there.
Besides, people say there's a presence here.
What presence?
This tunnel goes straight,
but a lot of cars crashed into
the walls for some reason,
so they had to make a new
road beside it instead.
Ever since, the bloodthirsty
ghosts appear every night
in search of cars to prey upon.
But that's not all.
Around here, there's a rumor
about being spirited away.
Sometimes, people suddenly disappear.
Aren't you going in?
Don't tell me you're scared.
N-No way!
It's only noon right now.
There's no way I'm scared!
It's… way darker than I thought.
The breeze is making an odd noise.
Hey, check this out.
A paper talisman?
It's to ward off evil spirits.
That must mean there's something evil here.
Нисиката's scared.
N-No, I'm not! That was only—
Look…
N-Now what?
What's this steel barrel doing here?
Wh-Who knows?
Check what's inside, Нисиката.
Huh?
You scared?
I'm not scared! I'll look!
I'll check it out, all right?
What's the big idea, Такаги-сан—
Такаги-сан? Huh?
Такаги-сан? Where are you?
Quit messing with me.
Didn't she say something about…
being spirited away… or something like that?
Такаги-сан! Answer me!
Такаги-сан!
Why are you screaming? It's just me.
Такаги-сан?!
You were looking for me just now, weren't you?
Huh? Is that what it looked like?
Damn you, Такаги-сан.
This was what you were after.
Hey, over there…
There's a hole.
Why don't you peek inside, Нисиката?
As if I'm gonna fall for the same trick again!
Don't mock me, Такаги-сан!
I-It's stuck! My hand's stuck!
How's my acting ability, Такаги-сан?
Now it's your turn to be scared!
Такаги-сан, it's like something's pulling me.
Help—
Ni-shi-ka-ta…
Did I scare you?
Wh-What is that?
I found it lying on the ground over there.
I'm glad your hand came loose.
Damn it. You just wait,
Такаги-сан. I'll get you this time.
You're way too scared.
We're back out.
Damn… I couldn't retaliate at all.
Hey, look, Onii-тян.
Another couple is on a date in the tunnel!
Shush/ Let's go.
She called it a "date."
What the heck was she was talking about, huh?
Hmm?
Wh-What?
You're blushing.
The test of courage was fun.
Uh… yeah…
It's almost noon. We should head home.
Yeah.
Where are you going, Нисиката?
Huh?
We're going in there again?!
You scared, Нисиката?
O-Of course not!
I met my quota for today.
Wait…
It's summer vacation, yet I still have
as many push-ups to do.
Summer
Science Project
"Summer Science Project."
Yeah, the consommé flavor is quite good.
You're lying. Your're teary-eyed.
No way. Mine's better than
your kelp flavor, Санаэ-тян.
They both sound awful.
There are so many flavors to choose from,
so why in the world would you choose those?
Your watermelon flavor is
playing it too safe, Юкари-тян.
Take risks in life whilst young, right?
Taking risks on popsicle flavors, huh?
Anyway, did you two decide on
subjects for your science projects?
Not yet.
Me neither.
What about you, Мина?
I'm still thinking, too.
Isn't there something easy to do?
Like, something I can finish in a day?
You should do actual research.
How about an observation diary on a dog?
Good idea! That sounds so easy!
They basically behave the same every day,
so all I have to do is copy and paste
and change the dates.
Write it by hand, at least.
Besides, a dog's day consists
of waking up, barking for a walk,
barking to be fed, sleeping,
barking for attention, and
barking to be fed again.
Why bother doing research about that?
You're such a stick-in-the-mud, Юкари-тян.
Well, she is the class president, after all.
She can't help it, I guess.
Right?
Damn these two…
In any case, are you guys doing your homework?
There's still time.
Right?
Just so you know,
you're not copying my work.
Huh?!
I'll do your independent
research for you in return.
On a dog, right? No thanks.
You say that now, but you're gonna
end up sharing your answers with us anyway.
She is the class president, after all.
Right?
Maybe I should do an observation diary on
these two for my independent research.
Water Tap
"Water Tap."
It's hot.
This is the worst day of summer vacation.
No way!
I overslept this morning.
Huh?
And then I had a flat tire.
But it's a good thing it happened on
the day we're not practicing tandem riding.
Такаги-сан said she's
going on a family vacation.
Was she coming back today?
I put off going out during the day
to help do chores around the house,
but they still made me go shopping.
This is the worst summer vacation.
I'll just write that in my one-liner diary.
Huh?
That looks like…
It's Такаги-сан.
She's back already.
All right, I'm gonna follow her.
Maybe I can find a
weakness of some sort.
Did she… I think she saw me just now.
No, maybe it's my imagination.
She noticed me!
But I can see your hat, Такаги-сан.
You're trying to surprise me, aren't you?
Time for a pre-emptive strike!
I'm gonna write that in my one-liner diary.
Sh-She got me!
Going somewhere?
Just grocery shopping…
What a coincidence, me too.
Let's go together. Tandem riding.
Like I said, no tandem riding.
Aww…
When did she find out I was following her?
Then, let's walk together.
Watch out, Такаги-сан!
Are you okay?
Yeah, today is the worst day.
You're hurt.
Ah, no. It's nothing. Just leave it.
No, you should wash it.
How embarrassing…
Does it hurt that much?
No…
It's just that I was already having a bad day,
and now I got injured, too.
I was thinking this is the worst
summer vacation ever.
Jeez… What should I write
for my diary homework?
Here.
Huh?
Uh, it's gonna get dirty.
Don't worry about it.
Th-Thanks…
That feels nice!
You tried to help me, didn't you?
Huh?
Thanks.
You should come in, too.
It's nice and cool.
Huh? No…
Come in already!
Cools you down, huh?
Uh, yeah…
I had a good summer vacation day today.
I got to see a certain somoene today.
Wh-Who?
I'll hand you your souvenir tomorrow.
Hey! Stop that, Такаги-сан, that's cold!